{
  "translations": {
    "en": {
      "fa1": "../../../AV/VisFormalLang/NFA/AutomataFiles/NFA2DFA2a.jff",
      "q1":{
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "[T/F] A DFA can proccess inputs from left to right or right to left.",
        "answer": "False",
        "choices": ["True", "False"]
      },
       "q2":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "DFA has a control unit (with states). The Control Unit defines what to do when in a given state and with a given symbol on the current square of the tape.",
        "question": "What state is the given DFA in?",
        "answer": "1",
        "choices": ["0", "1"]
      },
	"q3":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "DFA can only change state before going to the next letter to the right. That is, an acceptor does not modify the contents of the tape.",
        "question": "[T/F] DFAs can be used to add more letters to the given input.",
        "answer": "False",
        "choices": ["True", "False"]
      },
	"q4":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "The word Deterministic in this context has the particular meaning: When the DFA is in a given state, there is only one thing that it can do for any given input symbol.",
        "question": "[T/F] Given a string as an input, DFA can end in different states.",
        "answer": "False",
        "choices": ["True", "False"]
      },
	"q5":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "A non-deterministic machine might have some range of options on how to proceed when in a given state with a given symbol.",
        "question": "[T/F] A DFA machine may be a non-deterministic machine.",
        "answer": "False",
        "choices": ["True", "False"]
      },
	"q6":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "The word Acceptor in DFA means that: at the end of the processing the letters of the input string, the DFA can answer Yes or No",
        "question": "Suppose we have a DFA that tests to see if a string is a valid integer. What will be the result of giving it this input: 23213",
        "answer": "Accept / Yes",
        "choices": ["Accept / Yes", "Reject / No"]
      },
	"q7":{
        "type": "select",
	"description": "The word Acceptor in DFA means that: at the end of the processing the letters of the input string, the DFA can answer Yes or No",
        "question": "Suppose we have a DFA that tests to see if a string is a valid Java identifier. Which of the following will be REJECTED by this proposed DFA?",
        "answer": ["I love java", "123", "#variable"],
        "choices":["_hello", "I love java", "123", "#variable", "Not_an_identifier"]
      },

	"q8":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "Here is an example for a DFA:",
        "question": "Which of the following represents Q?",
        "answer": "{q0,q1}",
        "choices":["{q0,q1}", "{q1}", "{0, 1}", "q0"]
      },
	"q9":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "Here is an example for a DFA:",
        "question": "Which of the following represents F?",
        "answer": "{q1}",
        "choices":["{q0,q1}", "{q1}", "{0, 1}", "q0"]
      },
	"q10":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "Here is an example for a DFA:",
        "question": "Which of the following represents the alphabet set $\\Sigma$?",
        "answer": "{0, 1}",
        "choices":["{q0,q1}", "{q1}", "{0, 1}", "q0"]
      },

	"q11":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "Here is an example for a DFA:",
        "question": "Which of the following represents the start state?",
        "answer": "q0",
        "choices":["{q0,q1}", "{q1}", "{0, 1}", "q0"]
      },
	"q12":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "Here is an example for a DFA:",
        "question": "What is (q0,0)",
        "answer": "q1",
        "choices":["q0", "q1"]
      },

	"q13":{
        "type": "multiple",
	"description": "Here is an example for a DFA:",
        "question": "What is (q0,1)",
        "answer": "q1",
        "choices":["q0", "q1"]
      },


	"q14":{
        "type": "select",
	"description": "Consider this DFA:",
        "question": "Which of the following strings will be accepted?",
        "answer": ["101010", "111110", "0000", "01010"],
        "choices":["111", "101010", "111110", "0000", "01010", "0101001"]
      }
    }
  }
}
